35 millimeter slides
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- 35 millimeter slides, 2.1.5.1
  - Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)], 5 (Box 1585)
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Potala Palace], 17
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: Lowell Thomas, Sr. and Lowell Thomas, Jr. with three Tibetans standing in front of Potala Palace], 18
    - [Carousel number 9 [The Explorers Club (1908 - circa 1970s); first lunar landing (1969); Africa (undated); Tibet-3 slides (1949); T. E. Lawrence-2 slides (1918); Lowell Thomas, Jr. (circa 1962)]: African native with headdress and nose piercings], 19
  - Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949), 6 (Box 1585)
    - Beginning of Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949) [: Marco Polo painting], 1
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Men around camera equipment, Lowell Thomas sitting down], 2
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Mountain view], 3
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Rivers], 4
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Glacier], 5
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Snowy tip of mountain], 6
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: People forging river with donkeys], 7
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Dai Lama sitting on a couch with a dog], 8
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Lowell Thomas holding a little Tibetan girl], 9
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Man giving a speech at a podium], 10
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Lowell Thomas with T.E. Lawrence in Arabia], 11
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: T.E. Lawrence wearing Arabic garb], 12
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Inside of a cave], 13
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Close-up of man in front of plane, snow], 14
  - Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949), 7 (Box 1585)
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)] :T.E. Lawrence in Arabic garb], 1
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Logo that reads "EXPLORERS"], 2
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Group of men in suits talking together, Lowell Thomas at right], 3
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Mountain], 4
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Village in ? and view of a mountain], 5
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Room with world map painted on wall, fireplace, globe, tables], 6
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Airplane taking off], 7
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Snowy mountain], 8
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Close-up of a man], 9
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Man with tripod], 10
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Ice cave], 11
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Man skiing], 12
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Man in fur coat next to iced tripod], 13
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Man wearing heavy coat standing in snow], 14
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Group of men in suits standing around NBC microphone, Lowell Thomas second from right], 15
  - Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949), 8 (Box 1585)
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Group of men together formally for a photo], 1
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Lowell Thomas with man and woman on a ship], 2
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Close-up of a man wearing a fur coat], 3
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Man and woman exploreres with African natives], 4
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Book shelves full of books], 5
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Explorer with African native], 6
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Portrait of a man], 7
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Zebras in front of Mount Kilimanjaro?], 8
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Man and woman standing in front of vehicle that reads on door "Armand Denis Central African Expedition. Protect Wildlife"], 9
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Rhino], 10
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Lions in front of Kilimanjaro?], 11
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Archways over road], 12
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Camp set up on mountain side], 13
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: African sunset, giraffes walking by], 14
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Portrait of man in uniform], 15
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Room with a large globe in the center of it], 16
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Painting of a ship on water], 17
  - Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949), 9 (Box 1585)
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Man sitting], 1
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Beach completely covered with seagulls], 2
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Lowell Thomas with another man in front of world map], 3
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas, and two others looking at pictures on a wall], 4
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Close-up of a man wearing a fur hood], 5
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Portrait of a man], 6
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Portrait of a man in a fur coat], 7
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Ship on icy water], 8
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Portrait of a man in uniform], 9
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Close-up of a man's profile], 10
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Lowell Thomas and another man standing in front of red Navy helicopter], 11
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Dogs sitting on ice, ship sinking], 12
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Astronaut on moon, Explorers Club flag - "This flag carried to the Moon on the first Lunar Landing July 20, 1969. Presented to the Explorers Club by the crew of Apollo 11"], 13
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Five men stanfing together on a sidewalk, conversing], 14
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Foreign artifacts], 15
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Painted portrait of a man], 16
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Portrait of a man's profile], 17
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Doors opening up to a room with a large fireplace], 18
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Building], 19
  - Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949), 10 (Box 1585)
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Man on mountain side], 1
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Group of people looking at animal pelts], 2
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Lowell Thomas standing with three other men], 3
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Group of people looking at map], 4
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: People sitting at table, reading books], 5
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Man standing on a submarine submerged in ice], 6
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Statue of hands holding ship wheel], 7
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Painting of ship on icy water], 8
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Base out on ocean], 9
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Portrait of a man, note attached "Best regards to the directors, officers, and members of the Explorers Club - Lieutenant Colonel. U.S. Marine Corps"], 10
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: On the moon], 11
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Man about to scubadive], 12
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Lowell Thomas with the Dai Lama? And another man], 13
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Dai Lama seated in front of floral arrangement], 14
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Tibetan people riding on horses], 15
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: The Potala Palace], 16
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Close-up of a man's face], 17
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: Man in Nasa uniform], 18
    - [Carousel number 10 [The Explorers Club-explorers and exploration (circa early 1900s - 1960s); Tibet-3 slides (1949)]: African native with painted face, headdress, and nose piercings], 19
  - Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?], circa 1954, circa 1970s; 11 (Box 1585)
    - Beginning of Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?] [: Trees, road], 1
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Golf course], 2
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Snowy golf course], 3
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Golf course], 4
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Lake on golf course], 5
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Lowell Thomas riding in red golf cart with his dog], 6
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Lowell Thoams riding in golf cart with his dog], 7
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Side view of Hammersley Hill Estate], 8
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Backyard of house on golf course, garden], 9
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Lake on golf course], 10
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Tree], 11
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Lake on golf course], 12
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Three men in golf cart], 13
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Nurse with Frances Ryan Thomas in golf cart], 14
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas, a woman, and a man on golf course], 15
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas, a girl, and a man on golf course], 16
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Frances Ryan Thomas and girl in golf cart, Lowell Thomas standing behind them], 17
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Trees on golf course], 18
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Snowy golf course], 19
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Golf course during autumn], 20
  - Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?], circa 1954, circa 1970s; 12 (Box 1585)
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: People sitting outside at a table on golf course], 1
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Four men standing together on golf course], 2
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Four men standing together on golf course], 3
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: People sitting outside at a table on golf course, Lowell Thomas at the head of the table], 4
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: People sitting outside at a table on golf course], 5
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: People sitting outside at a table on golf course], 6
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Group picture on golf course, Lowell Thomas at left], 7
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Four men on golf course], 8
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Four men on golf course], 9
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Lowell Thomas sitting in snow with dog licking his face], 10
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: View of golf course with lake], 11
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Group of men on golf course], 12
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Lowell Thomas sitting in the snow with his dog], 13
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Choir singing in church], 14
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Birdfeeder and deer on golf course], 15
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Family of deer on golf course], 16
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Family of deer on golf course], 17
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Lowell Thomas sitting in snow with his dog], 18
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Lowell Thomas sitting in snow with his dog], 19
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Deer on golf course], 20
  - Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?], circa 1954, circa 1970s; 13 (Box 1585)
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Lowell Thomas sitting in snow with his dog], 1
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Lowell Thomas sitting in snow with his dog], 2
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Lowell Thomas sitting in snow with his dog], 3
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Lowell Thomas sitting in snow with his dog], 4
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Lowell Thomas sitting in snow with his dog], 5
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Lowell Thomas sitting in snow with his dog], 6
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Lake on golf course], 7
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Lake on golf course], 8
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Lowell Thomas sitting in snow with his dog], 9
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Road running by golf course], 10
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Aerial view of golf course], 11
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Golf course during the autumn], 12
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Lowell Thomas and two other men sitting in golf cart], 13
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Man sitting in golf cart with two boys], 14
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Group of men together for a picture. Lowell Thomas center back], 15
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Lowell Thomas standing with another man], 16
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: "Pawling-Patterson New-Chronicle" newspaper. Golf scorecards], 17
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Hammersley Hill Golf Club rules], 18